

# Van Dinh Nhat Minh

Fresher Software Engineer

Date of birth: November 17, 1994

Gender: Male

**Phone:** 01268624347

**Email:** vandinhnhatminh@gmail.com

Address: 601/8/11 CMT8 Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/minh-van-594a8415a

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Take advantages of data analysis skills & experience and understanding of business and technology to become a professional Data Analysis and bring a lot value to Comapny. From that, I will contribute to development of Our Company.

## **EDUCATION**

Oct 2014 - May 2018 University Of Economics Ho Chi Minh City

Major: Business Information And Technology

GPA: 6.8/10

### **ACTIVITIES**

Jan 2014 - Feb 2014 IC

ICIO 2016

**Operation Staff** 

- Organize the event for member who want to become a great CIO.
- Finding donors for event fund.
- Working with other university to organize the event.

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

2016 TOEIC Certificate with score 820 issued by IIG VN

### **SKILLS**

Social Media Experience	Have experience working on social media such as SEO, and advertising.
Coding and Programing	Have the ability to code independently with many language: python, R, C# , Autoit
Big Data Analysis	Have experience on big data, data mining, extract data from text data
Business	Have background and both business and technology.
Business Inteligent	Have experience working with BI solution Tableau
MS SQL	Have good understand about database, experience working with database, ETL and stored procedure,

### **INTERESTS**

I like music, travel and food...

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

May 2018 - Jun 2018

**BSD Solution** 

Tableau Developer
Main responsibilities:

- Implement ETL for client database.
- Solving problems with Tableau if any occur.Building Data Warehouse for client if asked.

Sep 2018 - Jan 2019

**Nexcel Solution** 

Application Support Main responsibilities:

- Recived issue from client
- Solving problems and hand over to responsible team.
- Recived Resoved issue , test issue and report back to client.
- Writing Script the test the functionality of database.
- Writing script to extract information from database.